# NICHOLAS TOBAT

## Front-End Developer

www.nickt.com

## WHO, EXACTLY?

I am a fully self-taught developer. I have learned the craft, found my own clients and built my professional reputation from the ground up. I have worked both at home and abroad in Australia. I am methodical yet agile in my work, and accustomed to and comfortable with a fast-paced environment.

Available for both freelance and full-time work.

## **PROJECTS**

#### FREELANCE GIGS

www.learnsensegrow.com.au

Occupational Therapy practice. Built in WordPress.

www.gordonandcocpas.com

Financial Planning firm. GoDaddy Website Builder.

www.wharley.com.au

Family bookbinding business. From scratch with Bootstrap.

#### PERSONAL PROJECTS

My Website (website)

I built a little something nice for myself: nickt.com

Documnt (web app)

Techno and concrete poetry.

Unsuccess (short story)

Life: an existential quandary.

Richmond Marathon (race)

Beat previous time (3:55:56).

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **FREELANCE**

*Jan 2015 - Present* Website Design & Building

#### **BACK OF HOUSE**

Aug 2015 - Present Street ADL

#### PROJECT MGR & SALES REP

Nov - Dec 2014 NCS Moving Services

#### TECHNICAL RECRUITER

*July - Oct 2014* Scaffold Labs

## PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- HTML(5)
- JavaScript
- CSS(3)
- Angular
- jQuery
- Bootstrap
- WordPress Python
  - worderiess Fycho

## **EDUCATION**

#### freeCodeCamp

Sep 2015 - Present Full Stack Web Development

Code School & Codeacademy
Sep 2014 - Present

## University of Virginia

Class of 2014 B.A. Foreign Affairs 3.4 GPA